We can edit news posts in multiple ways.
First way is to use the context menu.
Pretty much anywhere
the news item shows up to say,
Edit news.
We could do it there for the home
highlights.
We can do it from
the news list here.
The other way to do it is to navigate
to the actual news item.
And click the edit tab.
To edit this news item.
I'm going to show you, a new feature,
or at least a feature
that's easier to use now.
In the new version of the sites
and let's adding pictures and media.
So instead of being a two step process
like it used to be,
we can just go here to the insert
media icon.
And here we're going to have all the
images and documents from the site. Well
images.
And then there's a tab for documents.
We can choose an existing image here.
I like this image of my dog.
Or we can select a new file
like an image of both my dogs.
And this
target of text that I'm putting in here
is very important.
It allows
people is what a screen reader will read.
To people who have,
you know, vision difficulties
or any kind of disability
that, doesn't allow them to,
you know, access
the picture.
So would you want to have that?
You know, that alternative text
should describe what is in the picture.
Now we also have another new feature
called New revisions.
You can ignore completely ignore this
if you want to.
It's going to create a new revision
every time you edit,
something on the website.
If we click save,
we can see there's our image.
We can also go look through the revisions
and say, okay,
I want the one before I added the image
so I could revert to that.
I want to view it.
The image is gone.